ILGWU. Local 155 records 5780/054
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Informal Hearing and Meeting. Industry Committee No. 32 for the Knitted Outerwear Industry., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Recommendations of Industry Committee No.32 for the Knitted Outerwear Industry, Vol. I., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Recommendations of the Industry Committee No.32 for the Knitted Outerwear Industry, Vol. II., 1941 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Earnings and Hours in the Knitted Underwear, Outerwear, Cloth, Glove & Mittens Industries., 1939 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- NLRB Report of Proceedings. Amberton Knitting Mills, Inc. pgs. 1-192., 1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- NLRB Report of Proceedings: Amberton Knitting Mills, Inc. pgs. 193-288., 1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- NLRB Report of Proceedings: Amberton Knitting Mills, Inc. pgs. 289-465A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- NLRB Report of Proceedings. Amberton Knitting Mills, Inc. pgs. 466-664A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- NLRB Report of Proceedings. Amberton Knitting Mills, Inc. pgs. 665-881, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- NLRB Report of Proceedings. Amberton Knitting Mills, Inc. pgs. 882-936A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- NY Supreme Court. Appellate Division. Oakland Coat Corporation v. "John Doe"., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Forjardo Knitting Mills, Inc., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- "The Knitting Industries. Work Materials No. 80.", 1936 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- United Dress Manufacturers Association of PA. Spring Weekend Convention., 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Executive Board. Minutes., 1979-1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Knitgood Workers' Voice. Newsletter., 1937-1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Knitgood Workers' Voice. Newsletter., 1988-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Education Department., 1975-1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Joe Lombardo., 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Rules and Regulations of the Health and Welfare Fund of Local 155, Knitgoods Workers' Union., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Wage Raise Press Release., 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)